ANSIMA CIBALINDA Elvis

⚠ Goma, Nord Kivu, Democratic Republic of the Congo

■ansimapersic@gmail.com \$\+243 971 774 989

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ansima-cibalinda-elvis-9a658415b/

https://elvisansima.netlify.app, https://app.codesignal.com/profile/ansima_elvis_,



SUMMARY

Experienced PHP Fullstack Developer(LAMP & LEMP Stack) adept in all stages of advanced web development. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

EXPERIENCE

FullStack developer

Evoludata

- Contribute to open source solutions available including (Tiki CMS and WikiSuite) using PHP, Vanilla Javascript, MySQL, Git etc....
- Bug tracking and reporting in the codebase at evoludata.
- Working with the team to develop and follow coding standards and best practices.

FullStack software engineer

CTLCo Sarl

January 2022 - Present. Goma, DRC / Part-time

- Develop a FinTech Application and Deploy API for bank payment integration using top technology stack including CI/CD pipelines, Laravel and VueJS.
- Developed a microservices architecture and scaled the application to support high traffic.
- Wrote automated tests and optimized the code for performance using PHPUnit.
- Worked on the frontend using VueJS and integrated the payment gateway with the backend.

Electronics and IT Engineering Manager

CTLCo Sarl

October 2020 - December 2021. Goma, DRC / Full-time

- We have launched with success an HRM Cloud Application which gains clients and increased overall income of the company (https://demo.vantoria.ctlcosar.com).
- Build Saas Applications & Embedded solutions for Attendance System.
- Work closer with a team of developers for the design, development, and deployment of a cloud-based HRM solution.



Design and Simulation of COMPUTER VISION POWERED ROADS TRAFFIC CONTROL AND CAR SPEED TRACKER

Self • January 2021 - Present

- Develop A web application capable of monitoring Road traffic and control traffic light accordingly.
- A first prototype has been released and was able to simulate car speed tracking, plate number scanning and smart traffic lights https://github.com/ElvisAns/traffic_management_system/.

School Management System

Self • December 2020 - March 2021

• Build a school management system with attendance tracking features and financial management for administration https://github.com/ElvisAns/school-management-system/ .

Smart Health Monitor

Self • December 2019 - Present

- Develop and Implement an IoT system for Healthcare Industry using Electronic Sensor, PHP, Javascript and Data Visualization.
- A first prototype has been released. We measured Blood Pressure, SPO2, Patient Body Temperature and the data got displayed on a remote screen https://github.com/ElvisAns/smarthealthcare.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree in Electronics and Telecommunications Engineering

Minor in Software Development & IoT • Kigali Independent University • Kigali, Rwanda • 2021 • 4.3

High School diploma in Electronics Engineering,

Minor in Mechanical Engineering • ITIG Goma • Goma, DRC • 2017 • 3.25

CERTIFICATIONS

Responsive Web design

FreeCodeCamp • 2022

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/ansimaelvis/responsive-web-design

Modern Web Design

Gymnasium • 2022

https://www.credential.net/162d7fba-6223-45aa-8e2d-749c9be5eaf2

PHP FullStack Development

StudySection • 2022

https://www.studysection.com/users/socialMedia/NDc2MDI5/YW5zaW1hcGVyc2ljQGdtYWlsLmNvbQ==

Web Development

IBM • 2019

https://www.credly.com/badges/38808962-d8af-493b-873f-220441b75e9a/public_url

SKILLS

Front-End: HTML,CSS (SaSS. SCSS, Bootstrap, Bulma), Javascript(Vanilla, Vue JS & Jquery), ES6, Webpack

UI/UX: Photoshop, Figma, Canva & Framer

Database: SQL(MySQL, PostgreSQL) & NoSQL(MongoDB)

Backend: PHP (Native with OOP, Laravel, Codelaniter) & NodeJS (Express JS), Wordpress Plugin development

Devops: Cloudfoundry, Jira, Buddy, Gitlab, Github, Shell & Bash Scripting

Other: Agile & Scrum SDLC, Problem thinking and Brainstorming, Innovation, Communication, attention to detail, creativity and ability to work independently



CERTIFICATE OF EXCELLENCE

WE HEREBY CERTIFY THAT

ANSIMA CIBALINDA Elvis

HAS COMPLETED THE COURSE AND FINAL EXAM FOR

MODERN WEB DESIGN

Aaron Gustafson
Course Instructor



Jeremy Osborn

Academic Director

In recognition of the commitment to achieve professional excellence



Ansima Cibalinda

Has successfully satisfied the requirements for:

Web Development



Issued on: 11 JUL 2019

Issued by IBM



In recognition of the commitment to achieve professional excellence



Ansima Cibalinda

Has successfully satisfied the requirements for:

Artificial Intelligence Analyst - Mastery Award 2019



Issued on: 02 JUL 2019

Issued by IBM



In recognition of the commitment to achieve professional excellence



Ansima Cibalinda

Has successfully satisfied the requirements for:

HTML & CSS



Issued on: 18 MAY 2021

Issued by IBM



CERTIFICATE >

THIS CERTIFIES THAT

ANSIMA CIBALINDA ELVIS

ansimapersic@gmail.com

HAS PASSED THE FOLLOWING PUBLIC TEST ON MAR 14, 2022:

HTML/CSS, JAVASCRIPT, PHP, AND SQL, RANKING IN THE TOP 25%

TestDome is a provider of high-quality online screening tests for knowledge workers. TestDome uses work-sample testing methodology—candidates are checked through small samples of actual work.



ANSIMA CIBALINDA ...
HTML/CSS, JAVASCRIPT, PHP,
AND SQL

TESTDOME CERTIFICATE

freeCodeCamp(♠)

This certifies that

ANSIMA CIBALINDA ELVIS

has successfully completed the freeCodeCamp.org

Responsive Web Design

Developer Certification, representing approximately 300 hours of coursework.

Quincy Larson

Executive Director, freeCodeCamp.org